Guide to the Larry Bush papers, 1977-1984
Bush, Larry papers, 1977-1984
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Larry Bush papers, 1977-1984
7316
Larry Bush
7.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, drafts of articles, transcripts of interviews, photographs, audiotape.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection consists of Bush's personal papers and collected news articles. Subjects include AIDS, the Human Rights Campaign Fund, the National Gay Task Force, and the legislative and legal aspects of gay rights.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Larry Bush was the Washington D.C. correspondent for The Advocate. As a freelance writer and journalist, he published several articles in both gay and straight publications, conducted interviews, gave speeches, and published the Bush Report, which was concerned with gay political and cultural issues. He was also the Washington liaison for the National Gay Task Force.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection consists of Bush's correspondence, drafts of articles, transcripts of interviews, photographs, and an audiotape. Also included are subject files, clippings, reports, and articles pertaining to gay liberation, politics, rights, social and cultural issues, and journalism. Subjects include AIDS, the Human Rights Campaign Fund, the National Gay Task Force, and the legislative and legal aspects of gay rights; there are files on individuals, government commissions, and numerous other gay and lesbian issues.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Goodstein, David B.; Gay Rights National Lobby.; Democratic Party.; Human Rights Campaign Fund.; National Gay Task Force.
Subjects:
Advocate.; The Bush Report.; Gays' writings.; Homosexuality--laws and legislation.; Gays--Political Action.; Homosexuality.; Gay Men.; AIDS (Disease).; Gay Journalism.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The collection had little original organization. The materials were divided into two series: Larry Bush personal files, and an alphabetical subject file. More than half of the folder headings were assigned.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Larry Bush Personal Papers
Box 1, folders 1-52
Box 6, folder 1
Box 7, folders 1-36
Series II. Subject Files
Box 1, folders 53-60
Box 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6, folders 2-20
Box 7, folders 37-56
Box 8
Box 9
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Larry Bush Personal Papers
  - Notes, Handwritten and Typed; Drafts of Letters and Articles; Lists (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
  - Personal Handwritten Notes (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks (Box 7, Folder 17-34)
  - Personal Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9-17)
  - Larry Bush Personal, Including Financial Papers, and Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
  - Larry Bush Personal Documents, Photographs, Audiotape, Clippings, Certificates, Typescripts (Box 1, Folder 18-23)
  - Mailings, Newsletters, Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 24-28)
  - Larry Bush Finances (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Articles Published by Larry Bush (Box 1, Folder 30-35)
  - Letters of Complaint Against Larry Bush re: Published Articles (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Drafts of Articles, Interviews, and Other Writings; Handwritten and Typed (Box 1, Folder 37-44)
  - Typed Drafts (Box 7, Folder 6-10)
  - Handwritten Drafts (Box 7, Folder 11-16)
  - Bush Report (Box 1, Folder 45-49)
  - Bush Report (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
  - Speeches, Invitations to Speak (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Story Assignments (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
- Series II. Subject Files
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Advocate (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - AIDS - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 56-60)
  - AIDS - New York Times Clippings (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AIDS - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AIDS - Editorials (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - AIDS - Articles (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - AIDS - Mailings (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AIDS - Publications (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AIDS - Letters (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AIDS - Miscellaneous Transcripts and Articles (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AIDS - Miscellaneous Written Material (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - AIDS - Center for Disease Control (CDC) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AIDS - Congressional Action (Box 2, Folder 12-19)
  - AIDS - Gay Support Groups (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - AIDS - National Institutes of Health (NIH) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AIDS - Political (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - AIDS - Public Health Service (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
  - AIDS - Weiss Hearings (Box 2, Folder 26-29)
  - American Medical Association (AMA) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Amnesty International (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
  - Appropriations Committee Transcript (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Navy vs. John Baskin - Legal Documents (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Robert Bauman (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Blade Communications, Inc (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - Blade Communications, Inc. - Financial Papers (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Books (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Boston Gays (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Anita Bryant - IRS Documents (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - International Association of Black and White Men Together (IABWMT/BWMT) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Catalogs (Box 2, Folder 42-43)
  - Civil Rights - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights (LCCR) (Box 2, Folder 44-51)
  - Clippings (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Clippings - Gay Related 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 7-16)
  - Commission on Personal Privacy (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
  - 98th Congress (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - 98th Congressional Health Hearings (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
  - Constitution - Court Decisions (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Coors (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Court Cases (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Culture (Box 3, Folder 15-23)
  - Democrats (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Democratic National Party Conference, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - District of Columbia Sexual Assault Reform Act (Box 3, Folder 27-30)
  - Draft (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Family Issues (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Family Protection Act, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Federal and District of Columbia Crime Codes (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
  - Feminist (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
  - Films (Box 3, Folder 40-42)
  - First Amendment Survival Kit (Box 3, Folder 43-44)
  - Foundations, Grants, Awards (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - "Friends of Wine" (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Fund for Human Dignity, Press Releases 1982-83 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Samuel A. Garrison III (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Gay Academic Union (GAU) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Gays and Literature (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Gay Clout (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Gay Democrats (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
  - Gay Groups - Effects of De-funding (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Gay Journalists (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Gay Legal Organizations (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Gay Media (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
  - Gay Officials - Wayne Lerch (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Gay Organizations (Box 3, Folder 62-64)
  - Gay Organizations - Political, District of Columbia (Box 3, Folder 65-66)
  - Gay Political Action Committee (GAYPAC) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gay Press Association (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Gay Rights Coalition of Georgetown University Law Center, et al. v. Georgetown University et al. Legal Documents and Articles (Box 6, Folder 17-18)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL) (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL) - Board of Directors (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL) - Press Releases 1981-82 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL) - Press Releases 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gay Services (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - David B. Goodstein (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
  - Kevin Gordon (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
  - Governors (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Peter D. Hannaford (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Rev. B. Samuel Hart Nomination to U.S. Civil Rights Commission (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Denver Health Conference 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - History (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) - 1982 Tax Forms (Box 4, Folder 20-28)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) - Jim Foster's 1982 Report (Box 4, Folder 20-28)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) - Press Releases 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Immigration (Box 4, Folder 36-43)
  - International (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Key West (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Legal Services Corporation (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - LIFE Magazine - July 5, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Mailings (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
  - Management (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Miller vs. Rumsfeld (Box 4, Folder 51-53)
  - John Money, Ph.D. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Moral Majority 1981 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Mormons (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Movement (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Box 4, Folder 58-59)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - 1982 Crisis (Box 4, Folder 60-63)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - 1982 Crisis (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - CBS 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - International Association of Black and White Men Together 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Press Releases prior to 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Press Releases 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Press Releases 1982-83 (Box 5, Folder 7-10)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Press Releases 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Press Releases 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Jack Campbell (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - National Gay Task Force (NGTF) - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 14-16)
  - New Right (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters (Box 5, Folder 18-20)
  - Organized Crime Control Commission Report 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlets (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Political (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Presidential Candidates (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - Miscellaneous Press Releases (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Proposition Six - Briggs Initiative (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Redistricting (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Report - Interdepartmental Group on Unauthorized Disclosures of Classified Information (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Richmond - Human Rights Legislation (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Vito Russo - Stonewall Manuscript (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Sex Education (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
  - Sex Research (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
  - Sex Roles and Models (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Stonewall Gay Democratic Club - Press Releases (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - State and City Level News (Box 5, Folder 37-38)
  - Subject File (Box 7, Folder 37-56)
  - Subject File (Box 8, Folder 1-18)
  - Subject File (Box 9, Folder 1-28)
  - Uplinger Legal Material (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Washington Journalism Review (WJR) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - White House Conference on Families - 1979-80 (Box 5, Folder 41-45)